test sample from one of my videos
hello everyone! sorry for not being able to keep up with weekly uploads lol, i got a new computer!!
i had made some sketches but i can't bring myself to finish them
mostly because they are overly complicated and take way too long to finish
and also cause i get bored listening to the same section 10 times over lmao
so i decided to reuse the strategy that got me the weekly consistency
to make multiple projects side by side and finish whatever i wanted to
i might finish one project, and go back to another one that's halfway finished
and it's new to me again, since it's probably been a few days since i've touched it
it fixes the boredom really well, and i get more motivation to finish it
because it's only half the work. also i can polish things up and not get tunnel visioned
unlike after listening to the same thing over and over and over and over again. i think you get the point lol
i've been wanting to just, relax for a bit. i've been doing a lot lately, lots of goals set out
but sometimes all i really want is a break, and i can't seem to know how to take one
i wanted to make a piece that's more laid back just to relax things a bit for me
i hope you can also sometimes, give yourself a break, you deserve it! even if being productive is good however
we glorify productivity too much nowadays to the point of ignoring yourself, and i don't think that's healthy really. take care of youself aswell, and thanks for listening!